// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Period products are taxed and typically recognized by states as “luxury” or “non-essential” items.",
  answer: "True",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Food stamps cover menstrual products.",
  answer: "False",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "There is a link between menstruation and lost wages.",
  answer: "True",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Health insurance and Medicaid cover menstrual products.",
  answer: "False",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Over two-thirds of low-income women do not struggle to cover the cost of menstrual products.",
  answer: "False",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},

{
  numb: 6,
  question: "In 2020, Scotland became the first country to provide free menstrual products in all public facilities.",
  answer: "True",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},

{
  numb: 7,
  question: "In 2018, U.S. federal prisons made menstrual products free.",
  answer: "True",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "In the U.S., menstrual products are taxed in only 14 states.",
  answer: "False",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Period poverty is linked to symptoms of moderate-to-severe depression.",
  answer: "True",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},

{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Nearly nine in ten people who menstruate agree that period poverty is a public health issue.",
  answer: "False",
  options: [
    "True",
    "False",
  ]
},

];